Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
My name is Cheewa.
You should hurry home, Glasses.
Or you’ll get your money taken again.
Can you walk me out?
Astronomy Club.
I’ve been waiting for you.
But I don’t even know any of the planets you’re into.
Once you learn more about something,
you’ll feel even closer to it.
I’m not just into planets.
I’m into you too.
Can I hit on you?
Asking if he could hit on me?
What was he thinking?
Can I hit on you?
Hold on.
I’m a bit dizzy.
It felt like the world stopped turning
for a second.
The world can’t stop spinning, P’Niran.
The Earth spins at 1,675 kilometers per hour.
If it stopped spinning for even one second,
humans would all die.
What are you talking about?
Forget about humans!
No.
Huh?
That means I’d die
and you would too.
I can’t let that happen
because you and I
need to get together first.
Or at least,
become stars that shine side by side.
How’s he gonna hit on me?
Who’s hitting on who?
Damn. 7 a.m. sharp.
Is this the first time
you’ve ever been early to school?
What’s gotten into you?
Stop being dramatic.
I’ve shown up around this time before.
But what are you doing here?
In my club?
Does this club belong to you two?
Seriously?
Do you see anyone else using this room
besides the two of us?
Me.
Is something going on?
Are you okay?
Well…
Nothing.
Are you still worried about Auntie Tang?
I already set the record straight in the chat.
It’s a baseless rumor.
People will forget about it soon.
But what if they don’t?
How about this?
Let’s come up with a plan
to win those customers back for her.
How?
We play music to draw attention.
You have Pok and me.
Did you even ask me first?
Make yourself at home.
It’s my room.
Thanks.
Ugh.
I think that’s a great idea.
These two can sing and play guitar.
It’s just singing.
How would that make people buy her food?
Would it make them hungrier?
I know what to do.
Let’s give out free hugs.
Free hugs?
We give out free hugs.
What are you doing?
Be serious.
I’m just trying it out.
Whoever gets food from your auntie
gets a free hug.
But who will give out the hugs?
You?
Or you?
Definitely you.
You’re Auntie Tang’s nephew.
Besides, you’re a national team athlete.
Everyone knows you.
Come on. Just give it a try.
You have a tryout tomorrow anyway.
You could get yourself some supporters too.
What if no one comes for the food
or the hug?
I’d be so embarrassed.
You’re P’Niran from the Judo Club.
What are you afraid of?
I’d be more worried about
the canteen going crazy.
Let’s all give out hugs then.
Give the customers options, you know?
I think he’s the happiest about this idea.
He wants to do it.
Mr. Hot Stuff. Mr. Handsome.
What are the seniors
from the Music Club doing?
There are seniors from the Judo Club too.
You can tell them about the free hugs now.
Are those two clubs having a battle?
The Judo Club fights with music.
Go ahead.
Go. Let’s do this.
Hi, everyone.
I’m Niran.
I brought my friends to play some music.
I hope you all like it.
Actually, I have something to tell you.
The rumor about Auntie Tang’s
isn’t true.
Her food stall
is clean and safe.
She uses fresh ingredients every day.
Most importantly, her food tastes really good.
As you all know,
someone made up that rumor.
Oh, someone made up that rumor.
But never mind.
If any of you have enjoyed
Auntie Tang’s food before,
come enjoy it again today.
She’s waiting for you all with a sweet smile.
Well…
Today I have something to give out too.
Whoever gets food from Auntie Tang today
gets a free hug
from me and…
my friends here.
Any one of us.
Just get food from Auntie Tang,
and I’ll get to hug you, P’Niran?
That’s right.
I’m here for a free hug.
Huh?
What did you say?
I get my food from Auntie Tang every day.
Only from her stall.
So let’s hug now.
(Is the world… coming to a stop?)
(I guess all humans… are dying.)
(Just like… this kid told me.)
All done.
Thank you for the gift from Auntie Tang’s.
Today, her food tastes even better than ever.
And…
when you hug other people,
the world doesn’t have to stop spinning.
Just hurry up and get the hug over with.
Your food is over there.
Thank you.
Did you see Auntie Tang’s face?
She looked so happy.
The food sold out so quickly.
The juniors were fighting each other to buy it.
“I really want to hug P’Niran.”
It’s so annoying.
Please. I got plenty of hugs too.
Same with Thara.
Are you spacing out?
All that hugging must've
turned your brain to mush.
I’m not spacing out.
I’m just tired.
By the way,
Cheewa was the first to ask Niran for a hug.
Yeah.
I thought he was going to shoo us away.
Turns out he wanted a hug.
Let’s put these things away.
You okay today?
Okay about what?
About me hugging you.
Of course, I was okay with it.
My friends and I made that rule.
What were you thinking, though?
Why did you hug me?
Just claiming what I was entitled to.
You didn’t have to do that.
No one forced you to.
You could’ve just lined up
to get food as usual.
But according to your rule,
I had to get in line for your hug anyway.
I’d be at the front of the line too.
Tell me honestly.
Aren’t you shy at all?
You just told me yesterday
you were hitting on me.
Today, you already hugged me.
I’m not shy at all.
What’s wrong? Are you shy?
Why is it so easy for you to say everything?
Do you even have feelings?
You act like a robot.
Just because I’m not shy around you,
I seem like a robot?
It’s a mix of…
many things.
It’s not just about being shy.
If you don’t have bad feelings toward me
right now, and…
maybe you’re feeling shy deep in there,
that means I’m one step closer
to winning you over, P’Niran.
Are you the best in your school?
I’ve thrown people bigger than you.
It’s because you’re like this, Niran.
You have a big ego.
You’re too proud to lose.
But listen to me today.
What are you talking about?
If you want to make sure,
you can try hugging me again now.
Please.
Are you testing me or something?
Is there a camera somewhere?
It’s not funny.
I’m seriously hitting on you.
Ugh!
Fine.
Just do whatever you want.
Why are you smiling so much?
Someday, you’ll smile at me like this.
I saw the activity schedule.
Tomorrow, you have a tryout
for a spot in the Athletes' Village, right?
Mm, yeah.
Why?
Are you coming to watch me?
I have a test tomorrow morning.
I might not be able to make it,
but I’m rooting for you, P’Niran.
Fine. Thanks.
After the match, I have a reward for you.
What reward?
Can’t you give it to me in advance?
No. Wait until the match is over.
What if I lose?
Will I still get my reward?
Try winning first.
You got this, P’Niran.
There’s nothing you can’t do.
Even today, you put a smile back on
Auntie Tang’s face.
And mine too.
What’s with you, kid?
Go home!
Stop smiling already.
Go!
Are you coming or not?
Hey.
Everyone keeps saying
Most is going to win a spot
in the Athletes’ Village.
I mean, he’s really good.
He deserves it.
I could use a friend too.
Jace is here today, right?
We’re competing against his school.
Yeah.
You’re the one competing against him.
That’s why Coach made you practice
so hard.
Don’t underestimate Jace.
He’s tough.
I don’t think anyone from our school
could beat him except you.
Are you the best in your school?
Stop talking, Jace.
I’ve thrown people bigger than you.
Hmm.
Bow!
See?
This is what happens
when you miss practice.
I’m sorry, Coach.
It's not just about missing out
on the Athletes' Village.
You almost lost your spot
on the national team.
I’m sorry, Coach.
I’m sorry.
Hey.
I’m your teacher
and your head coach, Niran.
I’m not just anyone.
Don’t let yourself get like this
without anyone to turn to.
I don’t know what’s on your mind right now.
But just know one thing.
I’m worried about you.
And I’m always on your side.
Okay.
Yeah, he got beaten badly.
I bet everyone from Jace’s school
was laughing their heads off.
Niran must be frustrated.
He should’ve gotten a spot
in the Athletes’ Village this year,
but Most ended up getting it instead.
It’s no surprise.
Niran keeps skipping practice.
Soon, his best friend Thara will surpass him.
Trust me.
Soon, you’ll be better than him.
Hey, P’Niran lost.
How could he lose?
Really?
But he’s always won.
Ahem.
How’s my little judo athlete?
I heard you got beaten badly
by the other school.
Leave me alone, Oy.
Come on.
You lost. Just admit it.
In sports, you win some and you lose some.
Why are you making a fuss?
It’s because you’re like this, Niran.
You have a big ego.
You’re too proud to lose.
Listen to me.
You lost today. Your ranking dropped.
Your ranking dropped.
Loser.
Let’s go.
Where are we going?
It’d be better if you came and helped me
with some work.
Don’t stand here listening to
all this negativity.
What, four-eyes?
You just took him away like that?
What’s wrong with him?
So you really brought me here
to help you with work.
Yes.
I told you it’d be better
to come help me work.
I thought you were going to comfort me.
But you really brought me to work.
Do you want me to comfort you, P’Niran?
No.
Just asking.
You dragged me away.
Why did you just stand there
and let them insult you?
You didn’t say anything.
I just wanted to hear what other people think.
Why?
Well…
I don’t know.
I just wanted to know
what people were saying about me.
No one deserves to be insulted
just for losing a sports competition, P’Niran.
You argue with everything I say.
Why didn’t you talk back to the others too?
I didn’t want to lose.
I didn’t even want things to turn out this way.
But I can't keep practicing
the way I have been.
It’s too much for me.
Why couldn't anyone understand me?
Anyway, how did you know I lost?
I thought you had a test
and couldn’t come watch.
Full point!
Match over!
Are you sad that you lost?
Of course I am.
Why do you ask?
Are you going to comfort me?
I’m thinking about it.
Okay. So how are you going to comfort me?
Show me.
Want a free hug?
Huh?
Just like at Auntie Tang’s.
Are you crazy?
I’m not hugging you again.
Get back to work.
What? Why are you smiling?
Just keep working.
If you’re exhausted,
can’t you just tell your coach?
I can’t.
Coach will call me lazy.
He might have a good solution for you.
He might be waiting for you to talk to him.
Don’t keep it to yourself.
You don't have to carry judo all by yourself.
You've already taken on so much responsibility.
Try giving the people around you a chance.
Let them be a part of your life too.
Fine.
I’ll try talking to him.
You nag so much.
Why didn’t you press the elevator button?
Ugh.
Thanks, Glasses.
Oh, I forgot
Your name’s not Glasses.
♪ What's going on? Something’s shaking ♪
The elevator’s here.
♪ Like the earth is moving ♪
Okay.
♪ Yesterday, there was nothing there ♪
Get in.
♪ Why today do I suddenly care? ♪
So I told Coach directly that
I’m exhausted and need a break.
Yeah.
Damn.
Didn’t he scold you?
I was scared he would,
but he didn’t.
He said he understands.
And he adjusted my schedule.
Yeah.
You’re brave.
Who else in our club would dare
to ask for a schedule adjustment?
No one.
What do you mean by needing a break?
I’m exhausted, Coach.
I’m sorry I didn’t tell you directly, but…
I’m more exhausted than I can handle.
I’m stressed too.
I don’t think I can enjoy judo like I used to.
This is very normal, Niran.
Almost every athlete
goes through this feeling.
I’ll lighten your training schedule.
Would that be okay?
Honestly,
if Cheewa hadn’t encouraged me,
I wouldn’t have dared.
But you’re not quitting, are you?
If you’re going to make that kind of decision,
you have to tell me first.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Are you here for the lecture?
Wanna play basketball with me?
P’Niran and I live seven houses apart.
If you’re going to make that kind of decision,
you have to tell me first.
No, I’m not quitting.
Judo is still my favorite hobby.
By the way, he’s good.
That Cheewa kid from Grade 11.
At least, he’s good for you.
Could you check pages 2 and 3?
Teacher Boriboon, hello.
Hi.
Are you here for the lecture?
Great. Grade 10 is in charge of that today.
But wait.
Their class isn't over yet, right?
Their teacher still hasn't let them out?
Not yet.
They’re not here yet.
Oh, okay.
Actually, I’m here for—
You’re here for the lecture.
Today, the 10th-graders are going to
talk about natural satellites.
It’s actually very interesting, you know?
Yeah.
You girls should learn about that too.
How did you know I'd go find you upstairs?
I knew you’d probably want to tell me
about your conversation with your coach,
so I left you a Post-it.
Mm.
He really adjusted my schedule.
It wasn’t hard at all.
All this time,
everyone thought he was scary,
so we were afraid to speak up.
That’s great.
Now you won’t be so exhausted.
You’ll have time to rest and think about
what to do with the sport.
Wanna play basketball with me?
Who?
Me?
Yes.
With you?
With me.
Do you even know how to play basketball?
I'm decent, but I'm not that good.
Oh, you have potential.
I calculated it based on
the angle of incidence.
Stop it.
Just play basketball.
Don’t say anything complicated again, okay?
Okay.
Give it back.
Try and take it back yourself.
Deal.
Oh!
Parncheewa, are you sure you’re not good?
Hey!
What?
Be for real.
How did you end up losing to me?
Did you pretend to lose?
I didn’t pretend. I really lost.
You're better at the laws of motion than I am.
- It’s only natural that you won.
- Stop it.
No more explanations.
I don’t get it.
I just think you’re good at everything.
How come you lost to me?
I didn’t want to beat you.
See? You pretended to lose to me.
I didn’t.
You’re lying. You pretended to lose.
You’re accusing me.
I could report you to the police.
You’re just rambling.
There’s one thing
I want to win over, though.
Why are you smiling?
Stop it.
I can guess what you’re going to say.
I’m glad you know.
That makes me happy.
I might be pretending to know
when I actually don’t.
What?
Let’s do another match.
Come on!
Do you want to go singing after this?
Beat me for real, and I’ll go.
Deal?
Yes.
Come on.
I’ll start now.
Hey!
I can’t believe
the Astronomy Club room has karaoke.
It's for studious kids like us to unwind.
We may look nerdy,
but we all love screaming our heads off.
That’s why Teacher Boriboon
set this up for us.
That’s great.
Come on. Who’s next?
Go, Thara.
It’s my turn.
Cheewa, wanna sing with me?
It’s okay.
I’ll let you sing with your friends.
Sing with me.
I’ve already chosen the song.
Hey.
If you’re going to let Niran sing,
please just let me
bang my head against a wall.
Yeah, my friend here isn’t really good at
singing or dancing.
Hey.
If Niran is going to sing, let me know.
Huh?
You want to sing with him?
I’m going to pack up and go home.
Hey, my singing isn’t that bad.
It's really that bad.
Come on.
Let P’Niran sing too.
I want to hear it.
Alright.
Good job!
Thanks for making the effort to clap for me.
Thank god he stopped himself.
Don’t be sad, P’Niran.
Singing is something you can practice.
Did you know it took aliens a really long time
to discover Earth?
Huh?
It’s true.
They’re about 100 light-years away
from Earth.
They saw Earth 100 years ago.
Oh, come on.
You always give such long explanations.
Do you really think other people get it?
Let’s just say I’m bad at singing
and need 100 years to practice.
That’s how I take it.
As for…
your aliens,
I’d rather not know about them right now.
And you guys.
Take that!
Every single one of you.
Has the storm calmed down?
I was sitting here praying, all tense.
Please.
I was just singing, Hem.
Don’t tease our friend.
I thought someone was scraping their foot
against a sheet of metal just now.
Please. There’s no one in this world
who sings that badly.
There is.
There really is.
I’m not lying.
Come hang out with us again next time.
I mistook you for being too nerdy
to talk to normal people.
I’m just a normal human.
If you’re talking about aliens,
did you know that
I have this one assumption?
Stop.
Save that for tomorrow.
I really want to hear it, but I’m too exhausted.
I’ll wait to hear about the aliens.
I’m heading out.
See you. Bye.
You’re ditching us?
Yeah.
See you.
Damn, he’s in a hurry to leave.
Right?
Oh, by the way,
your house is on the same way as Niran’s?
Yes.
P’Niran and I live seven houses apart.
Damn.
What a coincidence.
But why did you two never meet before?
Because I leave early.
P’Niran leaves late.
Oh?
Oh.
Yeah, that makes sense.
True.
Learn to wake up early sometimes.
Anyway, get home safe.
We’re leaving now.
See you.
Bye, kids.
Try to show up in time
for the morning assembly too.
I still show up earlier than you.
So?
Let’s go home?
Which way should we take today?
Uh…
Can you lead the way?
What? No.
You lead the way today.
I’m always the one leading.
Let’s go that way then.
That gate is closed. Come this way.
It looks like it’s going to rain.
Once you’re inside,
I’ll know for sure you won’t get soaked.
You went from being the top rank in school
to where even are you now?
That’s why Thipok thinks
it’s better to make his own music.
But he sent his demos to a lot of labels.
He’s just waiting to see if any of them
call him in.
That explains
why P’Thipok has such a good voice.
Actually, Hem is a good singer too.
Everyone from the Music Club is.
Meanwhile, I hang out there all the time,
but I didn’t pick up a single thing.
In one ear, out the other.
Sometimes it comes out of my nose too.
P’Niran.
When we were in the karaoke room earlier,
I didn’t mean
you need to practice singing for 100 years.
Are you overthinking that?
Don’t overthink it.
I don’t even mind.
I don’t want you to take it to heart
and lose your confidence.
Cheewa,
look at my friends.
If I were going to get insecure,
it’d be because of them, not aliens.
Come on.
You’re right.
Your friends are way beyond aliens.
I’m hungry.
It’s not good to eat late at night.
I’m just whining. I’m not actually going to eat.
When you get to study with him, you’ll see.
He keeps wearing black sunglasses
when he's actually sleeping.
My friends and I tease him all the time.
Hey.
You should go home. It’s late.
Hurry.
The sky looks cloudy too.
It’s definitely going to rain.
Yes.
Mm.
Now start walking home.
I’ll wait until you get inside.
Why?
My house is right here.
I just have to step inside.
Because it looks like it’s going to rain,
just like you said.
Once you’re inside,
I’ll know for sure you won’t get soaked.
Fine, I’m going in.
You’d better hurry home.
I know you’re watching me.
Hurry home now, Glasses,
or I’ll kick you.
Go home.
Hi, Dad.
The school called to tell me
that your ranking dropped
and you missed your chance
at the Athletes’ Village training.
Yeah.
How could you let this happen?
Huh?
Aren’t you embarrassed?
You went from being the top rank in school
to where even are you now?
Well, the others are good too.
If the others are good, just be better.
If they train 10 days, you train 20.
What’s so hard to understand?
I’ll tell your coach to double down
on your training schedule.
Alright?
You’re not going anywhere over school break. You’ll practice every day.
No wasting time on nonsense.
I’m quitting judo.
I’m quitting.
I don’t want to do it anymore.
What are you talking about?
Huh?
You’ve put so much into this.
You can’t quit.
How much is enough for me to quit?
Just say it, Dad.
How much is enough?
I can’t carry the weight of your expectations
anymore.
Even if it’s just a sport,
you’ve dedicated yourself to it for so long.
Why are you being so rash?
Rash?
I’ve been thinking about this for a long time.
It’s not a whim.
You keep saying stuff like that.
Have you ever really understood how I feel?
Ah, I get it.
Your friends do music.
So you want to pivot.
You want to be a singer.
Make music.
Right?
Fair enough.
Leave my friends alone.
Then don’t lose.
If you don’t lose, I’ll let you do anything.
Yeah, I suck!
I could never be like you!
You don’t get this at all, Dad!
Do you even understand anything?
Screw it!
What are you looking at?
There are no stars right now.
Try looking up again, P’Niran.
What are you even doing?
There’s nothing up there.
There’s nothing yet.
But if you look up at the sky,
your tears will flow back into your eyes.
Or if you want to let them fall with gravity,
then just cry it out.
Why won’t you just go home?
I’m just here
in case you need someone at a time like this.
Why do you think I need someone?
I’m just here in case you do.
You worry too much about me.
You’re meddling.
I don’t want to see you hurting alone
on a night like this.
I’m staying here with you.
P’Niran,
I know it’s hard
to deal with everything in there.
But it’ll get better soon.
You won’t feel like this forever.
♪ Out of the blue, I don’t know what to do ♪
♪ Out of the blue,
can’t get any words out to you ♪
♪ Just one smile, and I’m blushing endlessly ♪
What I was looking at just now…
I was trying to see which star
would emerge from the dark clouds first.
It’ll come out soon.
In just a moment.
Mm.
I guess you won’t get to reward me, then.
I lost.
I was going to give you a gift anyway.
Where is it? Give it to me.
You get a free hug.
This isn’t a prize for the winner.
It’s a reward for being amazing.
If you know you’re amazing,
come and hug Cheewa.
♪ Is this love I feel, am I calling it right? ♪
♪ Is it why my heart beats faster tonight? ♪
♪ I see you every day ♪
♪ Yet I miss you again ♪
I still want to look at the stars.
Do you want to go to the planetarium with me?
Ugh! Why do I have to wake up early?
You really like this stuff, huh?
You’re smiling like a kid.
Can I be your little kid, P’Niran?
Why is Parncheewa being so clingy with you?
Just say you’re flirting with each other.
Don’t say that to him.
You’ll make him feel awkward.
Are you uncomfortable with me
hitting on you?
You’re down bad, Glasses.